Guide to the William Darlington Papers 1800-1863 MS 1165
New-York Historical Society
- Series I. Correspondence, 1800-1863
  - Vaughan, John, Dr. (Volume 3, Item 40546)
  - Ward, Townsend (Pennsylvania Historical Society) (Volume 3, Item 145)
  - Whiteley, R.H.K., Lt. (Volume 3, Item 106)
  - Wilson, William C. (Volume 3, Item 148/149)
  - "Carrie" - Miss C. Hitchcock (Volume 4, Item 154)
  - "Hariott" - Rachel Hayes (Volume 4, Item 1,2,3)
  - (Burnett) Fay, Eliza B. (Volume 4, Item 203)
  - Baily, Sarah (Volume 4, Item 190)
  - Balch, Augusta (Volume 4, Item 217)
  - Batchelder, Isabella (Volume 4, Item 112-134)
  - Bateman, Josephine C. (Volume 4, Item 173)
  - Beans, M. (Volume 4, Item 48)
  - Botanical Class, Young Ladies (Volume 4, Item 50, 51)
  - Botany Class (Volume 4, Item 53, 54)
  - Bouvier, Emma M. (Volume 4, Item 191-197)
  - Bromfield, Eliza (Volume 4, Item 167-170)
  - Burnett, E.B. (Volume 4, Item 199-202)
  - Carmalt, Rachel P. (Volume 4, Item 204-207)
  - Channing, R.G. (Volume 4, Item 72)
  - Cloud, J. Lizzie (Volume 4, Item 185)
  - Cloud, Joseph C. & Edwin C. (Volume 4, Item 185)
  - Coates, Sarah (Volume 4, Item 91-101, 102)
  - Collins, C. (Volume 4, Item 176)
  - Coyne, H.M., Mrs. (Volume 4, Item 18)
  - Crowell, C.R. (Volume 4, Item 78)
  - Curtis, E.V. (Volume 4, Item 198)
  - Darlington, Kate L. (Volume 4, Item 104, 180)
  - Darlington, Lessie (Volume 4, Item 187-188)
  - Darlington, Nellie (Volume 4, Item 188)
  - Darlington, Sallie P. (Volume 4, Item 73-76)
  - Darlington, William (Volume 4, Item 16-17)
  - Davy, Mary S. (Volume 4, Item 103)
  - Dickinson, Sarah, Mrs. (Mentoria) (Volume 4, Item 4,5)
  - Dillingham, Christinana B. (Volume 4, Item 182)
  - Dix, D.L., Miss (Volume 4, Item 105-111)
  - Ellis, M.A. (Volume 4, Item 166)
  - Embree, Sibbilla (Volume 4, Item 42-47)
  - Evans, Eliza A. (Volume 4, Item 153A)
  - Fales, Sarah K.P. (Volume 4, Item 63-64)
  - Fay, Elisa B (Burnett) (Volume 4, Item 203)
  - Fell, Sarah Ann (Volume 4, Item 60-61)
  - Female Botanical Society of Wilmington (Volume 4, Item 77)
  - Fothergill, John (Surgeon) (Volume 4, Item 47)
  - Galbreath, D.L. (Volume 4, Item 98)
  - Gilpin, Mary S. (Volume 4, Item 181)
  - Gray, Asa, Dr. (Volume 4, Item 136B)
  - Gray, Jane L. (Volume 4, Item 137-142)
  - Haines, A. (Volume 4, Item 62)
  - Hanford, A.G. (Volume 4, Item 214)
  - Hanford, Julia (Volume 4, Item 212)
  - Hanford, Mary A.C. (Volume 4, Item 211, 213, 215-216)
  - Harris, Sarah Coates (Volume 4, Item 102)
  - Hoopes, Margaret (Volume 4, Item 15)
  - Horticultural Society Committee Report -Comments (Volume 4, Item 208)
  - Hough, Jane C. (Volume 4, Item 83-87)
  - Hunn, Lydia (Volume 4, Item 209)
  - James, Isabella (Volume 4, Item 135, 136)
  - James, Thomas P. (Volume 4, Item 135A)
  - Johnson, Emily (Volume 4, Item 156, 158-161)
  - Jones, Amelia J. (Volume 4, Item 183, 184)
  - Juliett (Volume 4, Item A)
  - Kimber, Abby, Miss (Volume 4, Item 36-40)
  - Lambe, Catherine A. (Volume 4, Item 71)
  - Lamborn, R.H. (Volume 4, Item 186)
  - Latimer, J.R., Mrs. (Volume 4, Item 88)
  - Lea, Anna R., et alia (Volume 4, Item 49)
  - Lewis, Anna M. (Volume 4, Item 172)
  - Lydia (Volume 4, Item 89)
  - Maggie (Miss M.A. Cappuck) (Volume 4, Item 165)
  - M'Caulley, Mary S. (Volume 4, Item 77)
  - Missing (Volume 4, Item 41)
  - Morris, M.H. (Volume 4, Item 64A)
  - Morris, Margaretta H. (Volume 4, Item 65-70)
  - Muser, Emma, Miss (Volume 4, Item 174-175)
  - Newbold, Mary H. (Volume 4, Item 56-59)
  - Percival, A.W. (Volume 4, Item 13/14)
  - Phelps, Almira H. Lincoln, Mrs. (Volume 4, Item 20-35)
  - Pine Hall Seminary (Volume 4, Item 55)
  - Poem (Volume 4, Item 52)
  - Price, Rachel (Volume 4, Item 79-82)
  - Ralston, Anne (Volume 4, Item 143-145)
  - Randolph, C.J., Miss (Volume 4, Item 189, 189A)
  - S.J. T (Volume 4, Item 90)
  - Seaton, Sarah W. (Volume 4, Item 40827)
  - Sharpless, Emily (Volume 4, Item 7)
  - Sharpless, Joanna (Volume 4, Item 19)
  - Shinn, Artis L. (Volume 4, Item 171)
  - Shipley, Catharine M. (Volume 4, Item 163, 164)
  - Smith, John Jay (Volume 4, Item 210)
  - Southern Review Articles (Volume 4, Item 157)
  - Stanley, Catharine, Mrs. (Volume 4, Item 177-179)
  - Thomas, Rachel L. (Volume 4, Item 155)
  - Trist, E., Mrs. (Volume 4, Item 8,9)
  - Weitzel, Tabitta (Volume 4, Item 146-153)
  - Ziegler, Sarah A. (Volume 4, Item 162)
  - Affleck, Thomas (Volume 5, Item 143)
  - Allen, N.B. (Volume 5, Item 121)
  - American Philosophical Society (Volume 5, Item 142)
  - Archer, James (Volume 5, Item 11)
  - Armstrong, Edward (Volume 5, Item 221)
  - Atlee, John L. (Volume 5, Item 151)
  - Baird, Spencer F. (Volume 5, Item 190, 191, 192)
  - Barnard, General, Monument Committee (Volume 5, Item 225)
  - Bedell, G.T. (Volume 5, Item 137, 138, 139)
  - Bell, Thomas S. (Volume 5, Item 150)
  - Bohlen, John (Volume 5, Item 196, 197)
  - Brakeley, John H. (Volume 5, Item 128)
  - Brockenbrough, Austin (Volume 5, Item 22, 23)
  - Brown, David Paul (Volume 5, Item 147)
  - Browne, Peter A. (Volume 5, Item 131)
  - Carr, Colonel (Volume 5, Item 158)
  - Carr, Robert (Volume 5, Item 161, 162, 162 1/2, 163)
  - Cleaver, Isaac (Volume 5, Item 62-69)
  - Collinson, P. (Volume 5, Item 181-182)
  - Cope, Caleb (Volume 5, Item 206, 207/208, 209/210)
  - Darlington, Edward C. (Volume 5, Item 144)
  - Darlington, William (Volume 5, Item 79A, 104A, 170A)
  - Denick, W.S. (Volume 5, Item 106)
  - Draper, Lyman C. (Volume 5, Item 193-194)
  - Dunglison, R., Prof. (Volume 5, Item 142)
  - Dunlap, John (Volume 5, Item 201)
  - Elliott, Stephen, Bishop (Volume 5, Item 200)
  - Elsgood, Joseph J. (Volume 5, Item 202)
  - Elton, E. (Volume 5, Item 115, 116, 117)
  - Elwyn, Alfred Langdon (Volume 5, Item 109-114)
  - Emlen, George, Jr. (Volume 5, Item 155)
  - Fisher, Thomas (Volume 5, Item 169-170, 171)
  - Frazer, John F. (Volume 5, Item 154)
  - Gales (of Gales & Seaton) (Volume 5, Item 107)
  - Gibbons, Guillaume (William) (Volume 5, Item 13-15)
  - Gibbons, W. (Volume 5, Item 12)
  - Gilpin, Thomas (Volume 5, Item 174-176, 178)
  - Gordon, J.H. (Volume 5, Item 132)
  - Green, Traill (Volume 5, Item 136)
  - Haines, Townsend (Volume 5, Item 94-100)
  - Hall, Richard W. (Volume 5, Item 20)
  - Heister, James (Volume 5, Item 119)
  - Henry, Joseph (Volume 5, Item 228)
  - Hiester, John P., Dr. (Volume 5, Item 166)
  - Hine, L.A. (Volume 5, Item 127)
  - Hofland, T.K. (Volume 5, Item 108)
  - Hoopes, Joshua (Volume 5, Item 103)
  - Horner, Benjamin C. (Volume 5, Item 195)
  - Horsford, E.N. (Volume 5, Item 167)
  - Ingraham, Edward D. (Volume 5, Item 179, 180, 183)
  - Jackson, John (Volume 5, Item 156, 159)
  - James, Francis (Volume 5, Item 118)
  - James, Thomas P. (Volume 5, Item 157, 177)
  - Johnson, Joseph (Volume 5, Item 199)
  - King, V. (Volume 5, Item 83)
  - Kirkbride, Thomas S. (Volume 5, Item 160)
  - Kneass, Fullerton Tully (Volume 5, Item 75)
  - Kneass, William (Volume 5, Item 74, 76-79, 80-82)
  - Lavender, Thomas (Volume 5, Item 166A)
  - Lea, Thomas G. (Volume 5, Item 90-93)
  - Lewis, James J. (Volume 5, Item 232)
  - Lossing, Benson J. (Volume 5, Item 220, 221A-224)
  - Lowry, J. John (Volume 5, Item 122)
  - Markoe, Francis, Jr. (Volume 5, Item 120)
  - Marsh, Benjamin V. (Volume 5, Item 226)
  - Marshall, Moses (Volume 5, Item 149)
  - Martin (of Martin & Whiteby) (Volume 5, Item 188)
  - Martins, Charles (Volume 5, Item 101)
  - Matson, Morris (Volume 5, Item 104)
  - Mitchell, George E., Dr. (Volume 5, Item 16-19)
  - Ord, George (Volume 5, Item 140, 141, 145)
  - Parke, James Pemberton (Volume 5, Item 40552)
  - Paxson, B. (Volume 5, Item 84, 85)
  - Pearson, Henry Bramfield (Volume 5, Item 105)
  - Pennock, Caspar W. (Volume 5, Item 102)
  - Phelps, J.W., Capt. (Volume 5, Item 198)
  - Phelps, John (Volume 5, Item 123)
  - Randolph, George F. (Volume 5, Item 24-61)
  - Reed, William (Volume 5, Item 203-205)
  - Rogers, Henry D. (Volume 5, Item 211)
  - Rush, Samuel (Volume 5, Item 133, 134)
  - Sargent, N. (Volume 5, Item 213-219)
  - Sharpless, J.T. (Volume 5, Item 152)
  - Sloane, J. (Volume 5, Item 189)
  - Smith, John Jay (Volume 5, Item 184-187)
  - Smith, Samuel B. (Volume 5, Item 86, 87)
  - Smith, Thomas Lacey (Volume 5, Item 135)
  - Stoever, M.L. (Volume 5, Item 212)
  - Stone, Edwin M. (Volume 5, Item 168)
  - Strickland, William (architect) (Volume 5, Item 88, 89)
  - Strycker, L.H. (Volume 5, Item 227)
  - Sullivan, John M. (Volume 5, Item 231)
  - Tatnall, Edward, Jr. (Volume 5, Item 129, 130)
  - Thurber, George (Volume 5, Item 124-126)
  - Townsend, David (Volume 5, Item 148)
  - Tullian, J. (Volume 5, Item 74)
  - Waring, William (Volume 5, Item 233, 234)
  - Watson, John T. (Volume 5, Item 172-173)
  - Whiteby (of Martin & Whiteby) (Volume 5, Item 188)
  - Whiteley, R.H.K., Lt. (Volume 5, Item 165)
  - Whitmore, W.H. (Volume 5, Item 229, 230)
  - Wilcox, Samuel (Volume 5, Item 146)
  - Wilkinson, John (Volume 5, Item 153)
  - Williamson, G. (Volume 5, Item 21)
  - Winchell, Alexander (Volume 5, Item 164)
  - Wister, William W. (Volume 5, Item 70-73)
  - "Observer" (For the American Republican) (Volume 6, Item 167/168)
  - "Queries" (Volume 6, Item 101)
  - (Brass Field-piece) (Volume 6, Item 29)
  - Acker, Isaac (Volume 6, Item 249)
  - Affleck, Thomas (Volume 6, Item 129/130, 131/132, 133/134)
  - Andrews, John H. (Volume 6, Item 135, 136)
  - Armstrong, Edward (Volume 6, Item 190, 191, 192, 202, 206, 208)
  - Association of American Geologists and Naturalists - 1845 (Volume 6, Item 174)
  - Atlee, John L. (Volume 6, Item 225, 235)
  - B, H.A. (Volume 6, Item 76)
  - Bacon, J.B. (Volume 6, Item 295/296)
  - Baily, John P. (Volume 6, Item 169)
  - Baird, Spencer F. (Volume 6, Item 120)
  - Baird, Thomas H. (Volume 6, Item 209, 204/205)
  - Barnard, Henry (Volume 6, Item 370, 383)
  - Barnard, Vincent (Volume 6, Item 336, 348, 349, 361)
  - Batchelder, William (Volume 6, Item 143)
  - Bateham, M.B. (Volume 6, Item 117)
  - Betton, Thomas F. (Volume 6, Item 236)
  - Blakiston & Lindsay (Volume 6, Item 221, 222, 223, 224)
  - Booklist (Volume 6, Item 110)
  - Bradley, John H. (Volume 6, Item 387, 388)
  - Brakeley, John H. (Volume 6, Item 172A)
  - Broadside: Natural History of the State of New York (Volume 6, Item 181)
  - Brower, D.R. (Volume 6, Item 421, 422)
  - Browne, Peter A. (Volume 6, Item 220)
  - Browne, Peter A. (Volume 6, Item 90, 92, 93, 220)
  - Buckingham, Joseph T. (Volume 6, Item 33)
  - Buckley, Samuel B. (Volume 6, Item 359/360)
  - Buel, Jesse (Volume 6, Item 100)
  - Bullock & Crenshaw (Volume 6, Item 147)
  - Burchmore (of Ellis & Burchmore) (Volume 6, Item 5)
  - Burgess and Paine (Volume 6, Item 116)
  - Cameron, Simon (Volume 6, Item 290)
  - Canby, William M. (Volume 6, Item 254)
  - Carey, Mathew (Volume 6, Item 165)
  - Carr, William (Volume 6, Item 213)
  - Chapman, A.W. (Volume 6, Item 268)
  - Clemson, John B. (Volume 6, Item 238/239)
  - Cooke, Sarah (Volume 6, Item 177)
  - Cooper, Thomas (Volume 6, Item 9)
  - Cope Brothers (Volume 6, Item 288, 289)
  - Crosby, David (Volume 6, Item 177)
  - Cutter, Calvin, Dr. (Volume 6, Item 279)
  - Darlington, Edward C. (Volume 6, Item 194-196)
  - Darlington, Edward P. (Volume 6, Item 253)
  - Darlington, John Lacey (Volume 6, Item 13-15, 17)
  - Darlington, William (Volume 6, Item 31, 40-41, 86, 88, 91, 95, 98, 102, 158, 163, 166, 229, 232)
  - Darlington, William B. (Volume 6, Item 16, 281-286, 291-294, 297, 298/299, 302-307, 312, 316-318, 328-329, 335, 337-338, 341-342, 347, 352, 356, 367, 405-409, 411, 416)
  - Davis, John (Volume 6, Item 333, 339, 395)
  - Davis, W.W.H. (Volume 6, Item 325)
  - Dawson, Henry B. (Volume 6, Item 394, 412)
  - Dean, John Ward (Volume 6, Item 371)
  - Delavan, E.C. (Volume 6, Item 153)
  - Derrick, A.H. (Volume 6, Item 277)
  - Derrick, Philip (Volume 6, Item 8, 10/11)
  - Dickey, Jesse C. (Volume 6, Item 223A/224)
  - Dillingham, W.H. (Volume 6, Item 43, 44, 45/46, 47/48, 49/50, 51-68, 69, 70-71, 73, 75, 77-84, 121)
  - Dodson, R.B. (Volume 6, Item 102)
  - Downes, John (Volume 6, Item 144)
  - Draper, Lyman C. (Volume 6, Item 258)
  - Durand, E. (Volume 6, Item 105-106, 107, 114, 142, 353)
  - Ellis (of Ellis & Burchmore) (Volume 6, Item 5)
  - Elton, E. (Volume 6, Item 215)
  - Elwyn, Alfred Langdon (Volume 6, Item 125A, 126, 127, 128)
  - Emlen, George, Jr. (Volume 6, Item 200-201)
  - Espy, James P. (Volume 6, Item 108)
  - Evans, J.S. (Volume 6, Item 300)
  - Fisher, J. Francis (Volume 6, Item 74)
  - Flint, C.L. (Volume 6, Item 368/369, 375, 381/382)
  - Forney, J.W. (Volume 6, Item 297A)
  - Freedley, Samuel (Volume 6, Item 42)
  - Ghose, Ramdone (Volume 6, Item 3)
  - Gibbons, Henry (Volume 6, Item 103)
  - Gilbert, Howard Worcester (Volume 6, Item 118)
  - Gole, Mons. (Volume 6, Item 112)
  - Graves, William B. (Volume 6, Item 185)
  - Gray, Asa, Dr. (Volume 6, Item 261)
  - Grimler, Benjamin, Dr. (Volume 6, Item 152)
  - Hagner, Peter (Volume 6, Item 178/179)
  - Hare, G. Emben (Volume 6, Item 241/242)
  - Henry, Joseph (Volume 6, Item 274)
  - Herrick, Edward C. (Volume 6, Item 72)
  - Hiester, John P., Dr. (Volume 6, Item 215A)
  - Hinman, D.B. (Volume 6, Item 326/327)
  - Horner, John W. (Volume 6, Item 278)
  - Hough, Franklin B. (Volume 6, Item 262, 280)
  - Irvine, William N. (A.G.O.M.) (Volume 6, Item 30)
  - J.B. Lippincott & Company (Volume 6, Item 373/374)
  - Jackson, Halliday (Volume 6, Item 270)
  - Jackson, Samuel (Volume 6, Item 39)
  - James, Thomas P. (Volume 6, Item 115, 372)
  - Jenkins, Charles F. (Volume 6, Item 94)
  - Jones, Horatio Gates (Volume 6, Item 244/245, 248, 250)
  - Jordan, John, Jr. (Volume 6, Item 266)
  - Kennedy, Alfred L. (Volume 6, Item 109)
  - Kernot, Henry (Volume 6, Item 11, 183)
  - Kimber (of Kimber & Sharpless) (Volume 6, Item 164)
  - Lacey, Thomas R. (Volume 6, Item 20)
  - LeCatt, N., Capt. (Volume 6, Item 4)
  - Lindeman & Company (Undertakers) (Volume 6, Item 7)
  - Lindsay (of Blakiston & Lindsay) (Volume 6, Item 221-223, 224)
  - Linnean Society Constitution (Volume 6, Item 397/398)
  - Lossing, Benson J. (Volume 6, Item 264, 265, 310/311, 315, 322, 340, 362, 400, 401/402, 423/424)
  - Lossing's Pictorial History of the Great Rebellion (Volume 6, Item 400)
  - Luther, D. (Volume 6, Item 243)
  - Lytle, William (Volume 6, Item 203)
  - Macpherson, E., Hon. (Volume 6, Item 301, 415)
  - Maris, Jesse J. (Volume 6, Item 137)
  - Marple, David (Volume 6, Item 334)
  - McCorkle, William, Dr. (Volume 6, Item 32)
  - McIlvaine, A.R. (Volume 6, Item 212)
  - McKenney, Thomas L. (Volume 6, Item 186/187, 188, 189)
  - M'Clellan, R.M. (Volume 6, Item 425/426)
  - Mechlin, A.H. (Volume 6, Item 228, 229A, 230)
  - Meehan, Thomas (Volume 6, Item 141, 378)
  - Mendenhall, J.D. (Volume 6, Item 357/358, 364/365, 376/377, 384/385, 410)
  - Mercantile Library Company (Volume 6, Item 47/48)
  - Minshall, Edward (Volume 6, Item 176)
  - Missing (Volume 6, Item 96, 145, 207, 233, 287, 399, 418)
  - M'Minn, Jno. M. (Volume 6, Item 210, 227, 354/355, 403/404)
  - Mowry, Charles (Volume 6, Item 19)
  - Myers, Henry (Volume 6, Item 97, 98)
  - Neville, E. (Volume 6, Item 123)
  - New England Historic-Genealogical Society - Officers 1862 (Volume 6, Item 396)
  - Newton, Richard, Rev. (Volume 6, Item 193)
  - Niles, Benjamin T. (Volume 6, Item 246/247, 269, 273)
  - Noll, H.R. (Volume 6, Item 140)
  - Ord, George (Volume 6, Item 308/309)
  - Palmer, W.R. (Volume 6, Item 257)
  - Pamplin, William (Volume 6, Item 122)
  - Pearce, Thomas H. (Volume 6, Item 85)
  - Pearson, Henry Bramfield (Volume 6, Item 170, 171/172)
  - Phelps, Edward E. (Volume 6, Item 119)
  - Pittsburgh Canal (Volume 6, Item 38)
  - Porter, Thomas C., Prof. (Volume 6, Item 363/366)
  - Potter, Bishop Alonzo (Volume 6, Item 241/242)
  - Price, Eli K. (Volume 6, Item 214)
  - Reeder, Merrick (Volume 6, Item 151A)
  - Richardson, B.C. (Volume 6, Item 251)
  - Riley, H.A. (Volume 6, Item 146)
  - Ringland, Thomas (Volume 6, Item 242)
  - Roberts, Edward P. (Volume 6, Item 231)
  - Rock, Miles (Volume 6, Item 343-346, 350/351, 417/419)
  - Rothrock, Joseph Trimble (Volume 6, Item 413, 390/391)
  - Rush, Richard (Volume 6, Item 27/28)
  - Sands, Samuel (Volume 6, Item 211)
  - Schweinitz, Lewis D.V. (See also v. Schweinitz) (Volume 6, Item 34-37)
  - Service, Hugh, Dr. (Volume 6, Item 2)
  - Sharpless, Townsend (Volume 6, Item 216/217)
  - Sherman, John (Volume 6, Item 252)
  - Siegfried, S. (Volume 6, Item 174A/175, 219)
  - Silliman, B., Jr. (Volume 6, Item 173)
  - Smith, George (Volume 6, Item 420)
  - Smith, Jno R.C. (Volume 6, Item 87)
  - Smith, John Lawrence (Volume 6, Item 173)
  - Smith, P. Frazer (Volume 6, Item 313/314)
  - Smith, Robert P. (Volume 6, Item 138)
  - Smith, Thomas Lacey (Volume 6, Item 21-26, 379/380)
  - Snowden, James Ross (Volume 6, Item 255/256)
  - Southwick, S. (Volume 6, Item 104)
  - Spring, Robert (Volume 6, Item 319/320, 324)
  - Stebbins, L. (Volume 6, Item 323, 386)
  - Sypher, J.R. (Volume 6, Item 392, 414)
  - Tatnall, Edward, Jr. (Volume 6, Item 124/125, 139)
  - Taylor, Bayard (Volume 6, Item 272, 275)
  - Thomas, Philip D. (Volume 6, Item 234)
  - Thomas, Samuel B. (Volume 6, Item 267)
  - Thompson, B. (Volume 6, Item 1)
  - Thomson, James W. (Volume 6, Item 218)
  - Thurber, George (Volume 6, Item 118)
  - Tiffin, George E. (Volume 6, Item 6)
  - Tilghman, Benjamin (Volume 6, Item 18, 99)
  - Torrell, George F., Dr. (Volume 6, Item 148, 149, 150/151)
  - Townsend, Washington (Volume 6, Item 332)
  - Trimble, James (Volume 6, Item 12)
  - V. Schweinitz, Lewis D. (Volume 6, Item 34-37)
  - Van Leer, John F. (Volume 6, Item 89)
  - Warner, Thomas (Volume 6, Item 389, 393)
  - Watson, S.H. (Volume 6, Item 330/331)
  - Whitehead, William (Volume 6, Item 198/199)
  - William, Aaron, Jr. (Volume 6, Item 154-157, 159-162)
  - Wilson, William C. (Volume 6, Item 259/260, 321)
  - Wilson, William Darlington (Volume 6, Item 197)
  - Woodbridge, William (Volume 6, Item 180)
  - Woodman, Henry (Volume 6, Item 237)
  - Wyers, William F. (Volume 6, Item 263, 271)
  - Zimmerman, J.C. (Volume 6, Item 240)
  - Bache, A.D. (Volume 7, Item 152)
  - Balch, Lewis P.W. (Volume 7, Item 241/242)
  - Barratt, J. (Volume 7, Item 132)
  - Blackie, George S. (Volume 7, Item 251, 252)
  - Brackenridge, William D. (Volume 7, Item 158)
  - Breveton, J., Dr. (Volume 7, Item 72, 73/74)
  - Buckley, Samuel B. (Volume 7, Item 98, 99, 100, 101, 102, 103, 104, 105/106, 107, 108, 109)
  - Burrowes, Thomas H. (Volume 7, Item 246)
  - Carey, John (Volume 7, Item 176, 177/178, 179-183, 184/185, 186-188, 189/190, 191, 192/193, 194/195)
  - Carpenter, W.M. (Volume 7, Item 137/138)
  - Clay, J. Randolph (Volume 7, Item 93)
  - Cook, D.P. (Volume 7, Item 46, 47)
  - Dallas, G.M. (Volume 7, Item 50)
  - Darlington, Edward (Volume 7, Item 81)
  - Darlington, William (Volume 7, Item 2, 29, 81, 154)
  - Davies, Charles (Volume 7, Item 240)
  - Dickins, Asbury (Volume 7, Item 68/69)
  - Downing, A.J. (Volume 7, Item 196/197-204)
  - Durand, E. (Volume 7, Item 159-163)
  - Emerson, George B. (Volume 7, Item 217-218)
  - Engelmann, George (Volume 7, Item 168-175)
  - Engle, F., Lieut. (Volume 7, Item 70-71)
  - Evans, Joshua (Volume 7, Item 78-80)
  - Flanner, Henry Beeson (Volume 7, Item 247/248)
  - Foot, Samuel A. (Volume 7, Item 64-67)
  - Freedley, Samuel (Volume 7, Item 53)
  - Gallup, George G. (Volume 7, Item 56)
  - German Formulae (Volume 7, Item 62/63)
  - Gibbons, Charles (Volume 7, Item 165)
  - Goodrich, Chauncey A. (Volume 7, Item 219/221)
  - Hahn, John, Dr. (Volume 7, Item 1)
  - Hanson, Hugh Cooper (Volume 7, Item 227, 228)
  - Harris, Thaddeus William (Volume 7, Item 244/245)
  - Harris, Thomas (Volume 7, Item 41, 42/43)
  - Harris, William (Volume 7, Item 57, 58, 59, 60, 61)
  - Holcombe, George (Volume 7, Item 54, 55)
  - Ingersoll, Edward (Volume 7, Item 18-28, 30)
  - Ingham, S.D. (Volume 7, Item 3, 4/5, 6/7, 8-10)
  - James, Thomas P. (Volume 7, Item 228, 229)
  - Jones, Horatio Gates (Volume 7, Item 234-235)
  - Knigskern, P.D., Dr. (Volume 7, Item 140-151)
  - Lapham, J.A. (Volume 7, Item 82-92)
  - Latta, William, Rev. (Volume 7, Item 52)
  - Leopold, F.W. (Volume 7, Item 62/63)
  - Louisianna Medical College (Volume 7, Item 95)
  - Marsh, George (Volume 7, Item 167)
  - McKenney, Thomas L. (Volume 7, Item 156, 157)
  - Michener, Ezra, Dr. (Volume 7, Item 230-232)
  - Miller, Elijah (Volume 7, Item 166)
  - Neagle, John (Volume 7, Item 233)
  - Norvell, John (Volume 7, Item 33)
  - Patterson, Robert (Volume 7, Item 48)
  - Pickering, Charles (Volume 7, Item 75-77)
  - Pitcher, N. (Volume 7, Item 34)
  - Pleasants, Thomas S. (Volume 7, Item 139)
  - Pleasonton, S. (Volume 7, Item 40)
  - Porter, Thomas C., Prof. (Volume 7, Item 205-215/216)
  - Reinhardt, J.C. (Volume 7, Item 97)
  - Richardson, Richard (Volume 7, Item 239)
  - Riddell, J.L. (Volume 7, Item 94, 96)
  - Rogers, Thomas J. (Volume 7, Item 44/45)
  - Ruschenberger, W.S.W. (Volume 7, Item 164)
  - Sartwell, Henry P. (Volume 7, Item 133/134)
  - Skinner, J.S. (Volume 7, Item 35-38/39)
  - Stevenson, Thomas B. (Volume 7, Item 135/136)
  - Thomson, James W. (Volume 7, Item 153)
  - Townshend, Norton S. (Volume 7, Item 249/250)
  - Treadwell, Robert O. (Volume 7, Item 155)
  - Trego, Charles B. (Volume 7, Item 236-238)
  - Tuckerman, Edward, Jr. (Volume 7, Item 110/111 -130/131)
  - Ward, Townsend (Pennsylvania Historical Society) (Volume 7, Item 253/254)
  - Wayne, Isaac (Volume 7, Item 40863)
  - Wilson, Joseph (Volume 7, Item 49)
  - Wolle, Jacob (Volume 7, Item 223-226)
  - Wood, Alphonso (Volume 7, Item 222)
  - Woodbridge, William (Volume 7, Item 31/32)
  - Bethlehem-Plants (Volume 8, Item 15/16)
  - Bigelow, J. (Volume 8, Item 1)
  - Bromfield, William Arnold (Volume 8, Item 253/254, 255-258, 259/260, 261, 262-269, 270-273, 274-277, 278-281, 282/283, 284-287, 288-293, 294/296, 295, 297-300)
  - Collins, Laccheus (Volume 8, Item 26)
  - Curtis, Moses A., Rev. (Volume 8, Item 181-252)
  - DeRosset, A.J. (Volume 8, Item 196)
  - Harvey, Prof. W.H. (lectures) (Volume 8, Item 301/302-322/323)
  - Muhlenberg, F.A., Dr. (Volume 8, Item 324, 325/326)
  - Nuttall, Thomas (Volume 8, Item 27/28, 29-31)
  - Persoon, C.H. (Volume 8, Item 324, 327)
  - Schreber, J.D. (Volume 8, Item 325/326, 329-331)
  - Schweinitz, Lewis D.V. (See also v. Schweinitz) (Volume 8, Item 2-14, 17-25)
  - Short, C.W. (Volume 8, Item 135/136-180)
  - Torrey, John (Volume 8, Item 32-133/134)
  - V. Schweinitz, Lewis D. (Volume 8, Item 2-14, 17-25)
  - Wildenow, C. (Volume 8, Item 324, 328)
  - Allen, Jane M. (Volume 9, Item 600)
  - Allibone, S. Austin (Volume 9, Item 293)
  - Atlee, Sarah H. (Volume 9, Item 513, 514)
  - Baily, Mary M. (Volume 9, Item 614/615, 617)
  - Barrett, Sophie (Volume 9, Item 607, 609)
  - Blackie, Martha (Volume 9, Item 556/557)
  - Bolmar, Pattie (Volume 9, Item 558)
  - Boott, F., Dr. (Volume 9, Item 291/292, 312/313)
  - Botanical Autographs (Volume 9, Item 531/532)
  - Botanical Science-Historical Sketch (Volume 9, Item 618-638)
  - Bouvier, Emma M. (Volume 9, Item 591/592)
  - Bradford, Mary (Volume 9, Item 612, 613)
  - Carmalt, R.P., Miss (Volume 9, Item 486-492, 593/594)
  - Clark, Julia (Volume 9, Item 599)
  - Collinson, Anna Maria (Volume 9, Item 294-311, 314-330, 341-350, 352-367, 368-383)
  - Collinson, Louisa (Volume 9, Item 341/342, 351, 367A)
  - Darlington, Kate L. (Volume 9, Item 493-497, 498-501, 502-505, 506-509, 563/564, 567/568, 569)
  - Darlington, Lessie (Volume 9, Item 478-483)
  - Darlington, Mary L. (Volume 9, Item 562)
  - Darlington, Sallie P. (Volume 9, Item 484/485, 565-566)
  - Davis, Lizzie N. (Volume 9, Item 477)
  - Dulany, D. French (Volume 9, Item 263)
  - Eastman, Maria L. (Volume 9, Item 536/537, 541, 542, 544, 545/546, 546A)
  - Embree, Sibbilia (Volume 9, Item 597)
  - Fell, Edith N. (Volume 9, Item 409)